<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changes>
  <change>
    <version>*</version>
    <type>General</type>
    <comment>Began changing some of the file reading operations to check if a files exists before reading it.  This means there will be fewer unnecessary exceptions thrown.</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>*</version>
    <type>General</type>
    <comment>The program will now save the cache if the program fails unexpectedly.</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8110.6891</version>
    <type>Last.fm</type>
    <comment>The program will now make the last submission a day ago if it cannot find one from the XML file.  This is usually caused by the actual last submission to be like three days ago in which case the file quits keeping track of it.</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.4117</version>
    <type>Database</type>
    <comment>Now using two special strings to identify a null value in the database: ARTISTNULLNULL and ALBUMNULLNULL</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.4117</version>
    <type>Database</type>
    <comment>Changed that part of the program that fails when a song is added to the database without artist or album information.</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.286</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Changed the TabItemTemplate so that the item changes color on the MouseOver event</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.286</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Changed the background of the TabItemTemplate so that the entire tab registers a MouseOver event</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.286</version>
    <type>Database</type>
    <comment>Changed the error message of the hash fail so that it now outputs the filename</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8101.286</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Created a view change log button that links to a file on my website</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Programming</type>
    <comment>Created a change log file for the program.</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Changed various layout methods and removed some unnecessary items and holders</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Changed the style on the tab controls so that they have rounded corners</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Changed the control template for the tab item so that it binds its background to the TemplateBinding</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface code</type>
    <comment>Created the value converters for the top and bottom scroll buttons</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface code</type>
    <comment>Moved the converter code out of the similar artist code into its own file (soon will be own namespace)</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Moved the now playing section out of the tabs</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Added an about tab that will hold creator info along with version info</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>General code</type>
    <comment>Created the thread safe ObservableCollection class.  Will soon use this to create cache and submission visualizer</comment>
  </change>
  <change>
    <version>1.2.8098.3945</version>
    <type>Interface</type>
    <comment>Updated the scroll buttons so that they hide at the appropriate times</comment>
  </change>
</changes>